Alright
Ну что ж
What needs to be said
Всё что нужно было
I've said it all
я уже сказала
Your Highness need not rush to agree
Не спешите с ответом
Wan'er judges by actions
Я сужу по делам
Not by words
а не по словам
The news I overheard is
Я подслушала
Tonight this batch of money and grain
что сегодня ночью эти запасы
Will be transported by ferry
переправят на лодке
To do or not
Действовать или нет
Is up to Your Highness
решать Вашему Высочеству
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
I sent scouts
Я отправил разведку
That place
В том месте
Indeed has a secret warehouse
действительно есть тайный склад
Looking from afar
Я видел издалека
I saw them transporting supplies
как они перевозят провиант
I'm afraid after tonight
Боюсь после сегодняшней ночи
That warehouse will be gone
того склада уже не будет
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
Dispatch troops immediately
Нужно срочно выдвинуть войска
Without orders
У нас нет приказа
Where do we get troops?
откуда нам взять войска
The city defense troops
Городская охрана
Are all my sworn brothers
Это мои боевые братья
Don't need orders
приказ им не нужен
As long as Your Highness agrees
Только кивните
I'll lead them out immediately
и я немедленно поведу их
Privately deploying troops is a serious crime
Самовольный вывод войск тяжкое преступление
And you're deploying the capital's defense troops
а ты ещё и столичную охрану хочешь вывести
This matter
Это дело
As long as the evidence is solid
если докажем
We can explain to His Majesty afterward
потом всё объясним императору
His Majesty will surely show mercy
Он проявит милосердие
Turn major into minor
сделает из большого малое
At most
Максимум
I'll just lose one position
с меня снимут полномочия и всё
Your Highness
Ваше Высочество
This opportunity must not be missed
Нельзя упустить такой шанс